Committee of Correspondence Records, 1952-1989 (bulk 1952-1971)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS
  - International Alliance of Women, 1960-68 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - International Confederation of Midwives, 1961-68 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - International Conference of Free Trade Unions, 1961-65 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - International Conference of Social Work, 1962-66 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - International Cooperative Women's Guild, 1961-65 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - International Council of Jewish Women, 1961-69 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - International Council of Nurses, 1961-65 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - International Council of Social Democratic Women (U.K.), 1957-66 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - International Council of Women, 1954-69 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - International Federation of Business and Professional Women, 1953-66 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - International Federation of Home Economics, 1961-66 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - International Federation of University Women, 1953-65 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - International Federation of Women in Legal Careers, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - International Federation of Women Lawyers, 1961-65 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - International Union of Family Organizations, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Japan Society, 1954-60 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Liaison Committee of Women's Organizations, 1955-62 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Medical Women's International Association, 1961-66 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Open Door International, 1961-66 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Pan-Pacific and Southeast Asia Women's Association, 1961-65 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - St. Joan's International Social and Political Alliance, 1961-64 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Soroptimist International Association, 1961-62 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Women's Africa Committee, African-American Institute, 1964-66 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Women's International League of Peace and Freedom, 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts, 1960-68 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - World Council of Churches, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - World Union of Catholic Women's Organizations, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - World's Woman's Christian Temperance Union, 1953-61 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - World Young Women's Christian Association, 1959-64 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - United Nations, [see also SERIES III. CONFERENCES, SEMINARS, AND WORKSHOPS]
    - General, 1958-69 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Hospitality Information Services, 1961-62 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Consultative non-governmental organizations, 1955-64 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Status of Women Commission, 1955-68 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - UNESCO, 1954-68 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Technical Assistance, 1959-68 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - UNICEF, 1956-68 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - United States Mission to the UN, 1953-63 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - World Health Organization, 1957-59 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- SERIES V. CORRESPONDENTS AND FIELD WORK
  - Correspondents
    - General, 1954-68 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Interest research files, 1960-68 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Condolence letters upon deaths of prominent leaders, 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Excerpts of letters from correspondents, 1966-69 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
    - Holiday cards, outgoing, 1953-66 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Holiday cards, incoming, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Regions: Africa
    - ==Programs and proposals, 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Travel reports, general, 1957-66 (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
    - East Africa Women's Seminar, Nairobi, Kenya: conference material and correspondence, 1960 (includes Margaret Kenyatta) (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Status of Women Seminar, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia: Eleanor Coit, conference material, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - West Africa tour, Dorothy Height: correspondence and reports, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Sarale Owens, Field Worker
      - Tributes and miscellany, 1962-64 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Clippings and photos, 1960-64 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Field Worker proposal, planning, and job descriptions, 1960-64 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Incoming correspondence, general, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence to Committee and friends, 1965-69 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
      - Reports, 1961-65 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
      - Leadership training course, Nigeria: program materials, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Leadership training course, Uganda: program materials, 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Country files: includes correspondence and printed materials, alphabetical by correspondent, 1955-69
      - Algeria (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Angola (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Burkina Faso (Upper Volta) (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Cameroon
        - General (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Congo (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Dahomey (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Ethiopia
        - Correspondence, general (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - Fernando Poo (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - Field worker proposal (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Gabon (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Gambia (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Ghana (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - ==Ivory Coast (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Kenya (includes Margaret Kenyatta) (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
      - Lesotho (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Liberia (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Libya (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Madagascar (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Malawi (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Mauritius (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Morocco (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Nigeria
        - General (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence, general (Box 19, Folder 20)
        - Ademola, Frances (Box 19, Folder 21)
        - Alaga, Alhaja (Box 19, Folder 22)
        - Elumeze, Ezenwa (Box 19, Folder 23)
        - Essan, Wura (Box 19, Folder 24)
        - Harrison, Mabel (Box 19, Folder 25)
        - Onosanya, Oluremi (Box 19, Folder 26)
        - Snodeinde, Mrs. H. M. (Box 19, Folder 27)
        - Thomas, Yowonde (Box 19, Folder 28)
        - United States Embassy (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Rhodesia
        - Correspondence, general (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Agnew, Phyllis (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Baron, Mrs. Ben Rachel (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Chinamano, Ruth (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Hughes, Betty (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Mtero, Betty (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - Nyati, Louisa (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Price, Mrs. Basil (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Ramushu, Mrs. Musa (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Siboniso Women's Club (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Wynne, Helen (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Senegal (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Sierra Leone
        - General (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence, general (Box 20, Folder 14)
        - Bormann, Victoria (Box 20, Folder 15)
        - Coker, Esther (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - Domingo, Louise (Box 20, Folder 17)
        - Gulama, Ella (Box 20, Folder 18)
        - Hamilton, Patience (Box 20, Folder 19)
        - Johnson, Vivi (Box 20, Folder 20)
        - Karefa-Smart, Mrs. John (Box 20, Folder 21)
        - Savage, Laura Dove (Box 20, Folder 22)
        - Stuart, Lettie (Box 20, Folder 23)
        - Wright, Alberta (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Somalia: Unumb, Ellen (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - South Africa
        - Correspondence, general (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - van den Bos, Corrie (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Grieve, J. M. (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Gutsche, Thelma (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Kussel, S. (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - Lessing, M. (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - Richardson, Norah (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - River-Carnac, Dorothy (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Rosendorff, Reine (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Sudan
        - Correspondence, general (Box 21, Folder 11)
        - British Embassy (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - El Mahdi, Sarah (Box 21, Folder 13)
        - Gizouli, Sakina (Box 21, Folder 14)
        - Ismail, Fatima Talib (Box 21, Folder 15)
        - Khogali, Umsala Saeed (workshop participant) (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - Kunke, Laverne (Box 21, Folder 17)
        - Mekki, Zakia (workshop participant) (Box 21, Folder 18)
        - Nur, Mrs. Mohasin (Box 21, Folder 19)
        - Suleiman, Selma Mohammed (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Umbabi, Mrs. Sitt Amina (workshop participant) (Box 21)
      - Swaziland (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Tanzania
        - Correspondence, general (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
        - Akim, Bertha (Box 21, Folder 25)
        - Bulengo, Martha (Box 21, Folder 26)
        - Bwiru Girls' School (Box 21, Folder 27)
        - Chesham, Lady (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - Chitenje, Mary (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - Dastur, P.R. (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - Girl Guide Headquarters (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - Gumbo, T.C. (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Ibrahim, Mary (Mary's Institute) (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - Jaffer, Zehra (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - Juman, Kesi Salim (Box 22, Folder 8)
        - Kabisa, Matilda (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - Kasha, Bertha (Box 22, Folder 10)
        - Kassambala, H. R. (Box 22, Folder 11)
        - Khan, Nayeema (Box 22, Folder 12)
        - Kinabo, Koleta (Box 22, Folder 13)
        - Kingori, N. B. (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - Lameck, Lucy Salima (Box 22, Folder 15)
        - de Lord, Phyllis (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - Lupembe, Leah (Box 22, Folder 17)
        - Lyimo, Theresia Nd. Alberti (Box 22, Folder 18)
        - Mackeja, Mary Louise (Box 22, Folder 19)
        - Mandara, Victoria (Box 22, Folder 20)
        - Mandawa, Patrick (Box 22, Folder 21)
        - Masoud, Bibi Fatma (Box 22, Folder 22)
        - Matem, Lydia Daniel (Box 22, Folder 23)
        - Mgogo, Mary (Box 22, Folder 24)
        - Mohammed, Bibi Titi (Box 22, Folder 25)
        - Msaky, Mrs. R. Joseph (Box 22, Folder 26)
        - Mwaipopo, Ezerina (Box 22, Folder 27)
        - Mwaipopo, Janet (Box 22, Folder 28)
        - Mwegoha, Juanita (Box 22, Folder 29)
        - Pope, Amanda (Box 22, Folder 30)
        - Renju, Bassilla (Box 22, Folder 31)
        - Ronaldson, Mary (Box 22, Folder 32)
        - Robertson, P.A.P. (Box 22, Folder 33)
        - Sadikot, R.N. (Box 22, Folder 34)
        - Seya, Manida (Box 22, Folder 35)
        - Shaksy, Sanura (Box 22, Folder 36)
        - Shariff, Bini Khadija (Box 22, Folder 37)
        - Sheriff, M.H. (Box 22, Folder 38)
        - Siyovelwa, E.D. (Box 22, Folder 39)
        - Talati, F.S. (Box 22, Folder 40)
        - Thomas, Dorothy (Box 22, Folder 41)
        - Triplow, Mary (Box 22, Folder 42)
        - United States Embassy (Box 22, Folder 43)
        - Weidlund, Jane (Box 22, Folder 44)
        - Windham, Lady (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - Togo
        - Correspondence, general (Box 22, Folder 46)
        - Sivomey, Marie (Box 22, Folder 47)
        - Trenou, Marguerite (Box 22, Folder 48)
        - United States Embassy (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - Tunisia
        - Educators workshop, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 50)
        - Program, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 51)
        - Correspondence, general (Box 22, Folder 52)
        - Ammar, Nelia Ben (Box 22, Folder 53)
        - El Hamdi, Dalila (Box 22, Folder 54)
        - El Maherzi, Saida (Box 22, Folder 55)
        - Guiga, Chacha (Box 22, Folder 56)
        - Haddad, Radhia (Box 22, Folder 57)
        - Masmoudi, Dourdana (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Sassi, Saida (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Syryodipuro, A.S. (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Union Nationale des Femmes de Tunisie (National Union of Tunisian Women) (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - United States Embassy (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Uganda
        - Correspondence, general, A-M (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
          - General, N-Z (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
        - Angole, Margaret (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Astles, Mary (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - Banura, Joan (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Binaisa, Elizabeth (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - Bisamunyu, Irene (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Cave-Browne-Cave, P. (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Gee, Anne (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - Ghai, Neela Korde (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - Hassan, Awla (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - Jaffer, Zainab Sultan (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - Joan of Arc, Sister (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - Kabahuma, Ketura (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - Kaboggoza, Yemina (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - Kabuzi, Marjorie (Box 23, Folder 23)
        - Kagoda, Grace (Box 23, Folder 24)
        - Kajumbula, H.N. (Box 23, Folder 25)
        - Kalyebara, Amos (Box 23, Folder 26)
        - Kasule, Catherine (Box 23, Folder 27)
        - Kati, Shantha (Box 23, Folder 28)
        - Katuramu, Freda (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - Kibuka, Katie (Box 23, Folder 30)
        - Kichodo, Alice (Box 23, Folder 31)
        - Kigere, S. (Box 23, Folder 32)
        - Kiremerwa, Marjorie (Box 23, Folder 33)
        - Kironde, A.K. (Box 23, Folder 34)
        - Kisosonkole, Pumla (Box 23, Folder 35)
        - Makumbi, Eseza (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
        - Ministry of Social Development and Labor (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - Mitha, M.I. (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - Mubanda, Florence (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Mukuye, Marjorie (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Mulira, Rebecca (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Muwanga, Joyce (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Nansikombi, M. Rita (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Ndaula, Edith (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Ngatho, Zibiah (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Nsubuga, Dunstan (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - Okoth, Evelyn (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - Oomen, E.M.S. (Box 24, Folder 14)
        - Oyeru, Helen (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - Reynolds, Marjorie (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - Saben, Barbara (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - Sandhu, J. (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - Semambo, A.P.W. (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - Senoga, Edith (Box 24, Folder 20)
        - Shonby, Catherine (Box 24, Folder 21)
        - Tacchi, Helen (Box 24, Folder 22)
        - Uganda Council of Women (Box 24, Folder 23)
        - United States Embassy (Box 24, Folder 24)
        - Visram, Sugra (Box 24, Folder 25)
        - Wasonga, Janet (Box 24, Folder 26)
        - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 24, Folder 27)
        - Zikusoka, K.B. (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Upper Volta, [see Burkina Faso] (Box 24)
      - Zambia
        - Correspondence, general (Box 24, Folder 29)
        - Bowen, Joan (Box 24, Folder 30)
        - Bulaway, Linah (Box 24, Folder 31)
        - Chanda, Joyce (Box 24, Folder 32)
        - Chifunda, Mary (Box 24, Folder 33)
        - Chilesne, Martha (Box 24, Folder 34)
        - Kalulu, Rachel (Box 24, Folder 35)
        - Kaunda, Josina (Box 24, Folder 36)
        - Konie, Gwendoline N.C. (Box 24, Folder 37)
        - M'Kele, E. Thako (Box 24, Folder 38)
        - Paul, E.M. (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Zimbabwe, [see Rhodesia] (Box 24)
  - Regions: Asia
    - Travel reports, general, 1955-68 (Box 24, Folder 40-42)
    - Country files
      - Afghanistan
        - Correspondence, general (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - United States Embassy (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Burma (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Cambodia (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Ceylon
        - Correspondence, general (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - United States Embassy (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Hong Kong (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - India (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
      - ==Indonesia (Box 25, Folder 11-12)
        - Correspondence, general (Box 25, Folder 13-14)
        - United States Embassy (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Korea (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Laos (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Malaya (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Nepal (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Pakistan
        - Correspondence, general (includes Liaquat Ali Khan) (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
        - All Pakistan Women's Association (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Philippines
        - Correspondence, general (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Balboa, Fernanda (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Benavides, Enriqueta (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Benitez, Helena (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - del Carmen, Aurea (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - Catolico, Paz (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Ilog, Visitacion (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Nakpil, Carmen (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Plang, Bai (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Singapore
        - Correspondence, general (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Eu, Phyllis (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - Leng, Seow Peck (Box 26, Folder 19)
        - Pan-Pacific and Southeast Asia Women's Association of Singapore (Box 26, Folder 20)
        - Siraj, M. (Box 26, Folder 21)
        - Smith, Margaret (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Taiwan
        - Correspondence, general (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Chang, Mary (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Cheng, Chu-Sheng Yeh (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Hu, Elizabeth (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Lee, Helen Hsieh-chin Yeh (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - Tseng, Pao Swen (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Union of Women's Associations, Republic of China (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - United States Embassy (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Thailand
        - Correspondence, general (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Apaivongse, Lakka (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - Baedyagun, Khunying (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Chaiyasut, Nantanee (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Chartikavanij, Sumali (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Diskul, Poon (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Hoskins, Marilyn (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - Kasemsri, Sermsri (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - Koonvisal, Orawan (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Malakul, Pin (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - Meesook, Ambhorn (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - Moses, Dorothy (United Nations) (Box 27, Folder 20)
        - Nilubol, M.L. Anong (Box 27, Folder 21)
        - Pintong, Nilawan (Box 27, Folder 22)
        - Polpat-Pichen, Sukhon (Box 27, Folder 23)
        - Purachatra, Princess Prem (Box 27, Folder 24)
        - Sibunruang, J. Kasem (Box 27, Folder 25)
        - Srichandra, Jean (Box 27, Folder 26)
        - Suprabhatananda, Nandaka (Box 27, Folder 27)
        - United States Embassy (Box 27, Folder 28)
        - Vejjabul, Phiera Hoon (Box 27, Folder 29)
        - Vil, Kanok Samsen (Box 27, Folder 30)
        - Visessurakarn, Suparb (Box 27, Folder 31)
        - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Vietnam
        - Correspondence, general (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
        - An, Le Thi (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - Cao, Blanche (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - United States Embassy (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Regions: Europe
    - Travel reports, general, 1953-67 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
    - Country files
      - Austria (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Belgium (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Cyprus (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Denmark (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Finland (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - France (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Germany (Box 28, Folder 14-15)
      - Great Britain
        - Correspondence, general
          - A-B (Box 28, Folder 16)
          - C-Z (Box 29, Folder 1-8)
        - Ahmed, Ruth (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Ashby, M. Corbett (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Bagwanden, E.M. (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - Blackman, Albertha (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Bosanquet, C.I.C. (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - Bush, Amy (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - Casinader, Laurel (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Chute, Emerin (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - Collisson, Chave (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Cullen, J.S. (Box 29, Folder 18)
        - Davies, Vera (Box 29, Folder 19)
        - Deane, Nora (Box 29, Folder 20)
        - Domb, M.W. (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Duguid, Margaret (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Dunbar, Elsa (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Eden, M. (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Elliot, Katherine (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Garnett, S.E. (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - Gibbs, Evelyn (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Gibson, Isobel (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Grace, Barbara (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - Gwilliam, Freda (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Hickman, Olive (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Hodge, C.E. (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - Holmes, Winifred (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - Ingledew, M. (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - Isaacs, Margot (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - Josten, Patricia (Box 30, Folder 16)
        - Kenyon, Nellie (Box 30, Folder 17)
        - Kirby, A.F. (Box 30, Folder 18)
        - Leslie, Sheila (Box 30, Folder 19)
        - Levy, Kathleen (Box 30, Folder 20)
        - Mallorie, Margaret (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - National Council of Women of Great Britain (Box 30, Folder 22)
        - Nightingale, E. Constance (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - Ogot, Pamela (Box 30, Folder 24)
        - Playfair, M.J. (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - Porter, Jennifer M.P. (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Saran, Mary (Box 30, Folder 27)
        - du Sautoy, Peter (Box 30, Folder 28)
        - Scottish Women's Rural Institutes (Box 30, Folder 29)
        - Stanley, Alisa (Box 30, Folder 30)
        - Streater, Nermin (Box 30, Folder 31)
        - Thorne, Diana (Box 30, Folder 32)
        - Tomlinson, Ruth (Box 30, Folder 33)
        - United States Embassy (Box 30, Folder 34)
        - Vickers, Joan (Box 30, Folder 35)
        - Waller, Elizabeth (Box 30, Folder 36)
        - Whittick, Helen (Box 30, Folder 37)
        - Women's Council (Box 30, Folder 38)
        - Women's Freedom League (Box 30, Folder 39)
        - Women's Royal Voluntary Service (Box 30, Folder 40)
        - Wood, J.A. (Box 30, Folder 42)
        - World Goodwill (Box 30, Folder 43)
        - Young, Edith (Box 30, Folder 44)
        - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - Greece (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      - Iceland (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Ireland (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Italy (Box 31, Folder 5-7)
      - Lichtenstein (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Netherlands (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Norway (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Portugal (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Spain
        - Correspondence, general (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Aguado, Dolores Pala (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Medina, Matilde (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Salas, Piedad (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Sweden
        - Correspondence, general (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - Anrep, Edith (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - Ekendahl, Sigrid (Box 31, Folder 18)
        - Mattson, Lisa (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - Rydh, Hanna (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - Wiklund, Gertrud (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Switzerland
        - Correspondence, general (Box 31, Folder 22)
        - Barot, Madeleine (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Egg, Marian (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Hagmann, Elide (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Henrici, Marguerite (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Hill, Penelope Wood (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - International Union for Child Welfare (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Johnstone, Elizabeth (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Koopman, Jetty (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - Medical Women's International Association (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Moser, A.E. (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Naegeli, Gisela (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Rimondini-Schnitter, Irmgard (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Rochedieu, A.E. (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Ruckstuhl-Thalmessinger, Lotti (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Union Mondiale de la Femme (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Turkey
        - Correspondence, general (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - Abadan, Nermin (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Arpacioglu, Nermin (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Boray, Bayan Hacer H.B. (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - Bozoglu, Saade (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Ertung, Handan (Box 32, Folder 22)
        - Gursaytrak, Suna Kili (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - Katipoglu, Sadun (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - Kunt, Suheyla (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - Ozkan, Mehida (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - Parla, Perihan (Box 32, Folder 27)
        - Pulat, Nihal (Box 32, Folder 28)
        - Seden, Fahrunnisa (Box 32, Folder 29)
        - Somersan, Bayan Roksan (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - Textas, Nazli (Box 32, Folder 31)
        - Tlabar, Nazli (Box 32, Folder 32)
        - United States Embassy (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - Yenal, Nurcemal (Box 32, Folder 34)